Finding Aid for Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio recordings on cassettes 1975-2001
  - Martin Luther King Day
    - Charles Moody and Lemuel A. Johnson: Moody: A Celebration of Our Interconnectedness; Johnson: The Changing Forms of Racism: Historical and Current Perspectives 1988-01-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-332-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-332-2
    - Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis: Tribute to King 1988-01-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-333-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-333-2
    - Ernest Wilson and Omari Kokole: MLK Lecture 1988-01-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-334-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-334-2
    - Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby: MLK Day 1988-01-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-335-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-335-2
    - Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby: MLK Day 1988-01-18, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-336-1
    - Frank Ellis: Dreams and accomplishments: The tortuous path to achieving equity in the health care system 1988-01-19, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-337-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-337-2
    - Robert Christman: Martin Luther King Day 1989-01-16, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-338-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-338-2
    - Artists for Cultural Equity: I, too, Sing America 1990-01-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-339-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-339-2
    - Haki Madhabuti: MLK Day 1990-01-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-340-1
    - Earl Lewis, Rebecca Scott and Martha Norman: Race, Social Change and the Search for Power 1990-01-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-341-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-341-2
    - Earl Lewis, Rebecca Scott and Martha Norman: Race, Social Change and the Search for Power 1990-01-15, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-342-1
    - Ethnic Issues in the Media 1991-01-21, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-343-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-343-2
    - Michael Blakely: Struggle for Human Rights 1991-01-21, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-344-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-344-2
    - James Forman: Civil Rights Movement in the 1950s and 1960s 1991-01-21, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-345-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-345-2
    - Leith Mullins: MLK Day 1991-01-21, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-346-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-346-2
    - Leith Mullins: MLK Day 1991-01-21, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-347-1
    - Benjamin Hooks: The Significance of Martin Luther King Day 1992-01-20, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-348-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-348-2
    - Haki R. Madhubuti: The New Black Nationalism 1992-01-20, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-349-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-349-2
    - Anthony Ingram: The Commitments of Leadership 1992-01-20, audiocassette (Box 33)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-350-1
  - CAAS Mini-course 324: Black Educational Achievement over the Life-Course
    - Margaret Beale Spencer: The preschool and early childhood years 1988-03-03, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-351-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-351-2
    - Margaret Beale Spencer: The preschool and early childhood years 1988-03-03, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-352-1
    - Reginald Clark: Family life and school achievement: Why poor Black children succeed or fail 1988-03-10, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-353-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-353-2
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years 1988-03-17, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-354-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-354-2
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years 1988-03-17, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-355-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-355-2
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years 1988-03-17, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-356-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-356-2
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years circa 1988-03-17, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-357-1
    - Edgar G. Epps: The Senior High Years: Correlates of Academic Achievement Among Black Youth in America 1988-03-24, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-358-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-358-2
    - Walter Allen: Institutional context, interpersonal relationships, personality orientation and black student academic achievement in college 1988-03-31, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-359-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-359-2
    - Vincent P. Franklin: The talented tenth: Afro-American Intellectuals in the Twentieth Century 1988-04-14, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-360-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-360-2
    - Vincent P. Franklin: The talented tenth: Afro-American Intellectuals in the Twentieth Century 1988-04-14, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-361-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-361-2
  - Chronological events
    - Eunice Royster: What's Unique about Black Leadership 1983-07-01, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-362-1
    - Walter R. Allen, Masipula Sithole, David Gordon, Sulayman Nyang, Ron Walters and Ali A. Mazrui: Reflections on Ali Marui's 'The Africans' TV Series 1986-12-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-363-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-363-2
    - Ali Mazrui: Africa's Triple Heritage 1986-11-21, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-364-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-364-2
    - Ted Sevransky: Racial Jokes 1987-02-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-365-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-365-2
    - Michael Dawkins: Michael Dawson 1987-02-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-366-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-366-2
    - John Behee: Black Lettermen Athletes of U-M 1987-02-13, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-367-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-367-2
    - Jon Onye Lockard: An African Journey 1987-02-24, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-368-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-368-2
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings 1987-03-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-369-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-369-2
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings 1987-03-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-370-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-370-2
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings 1987-03-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-371-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-371-2
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings 1987-03-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-372-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-372-2
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings 1987-03-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-373-1
    - Michael Awkward: Double Consciousness and Afro-American Women's Novels 1987-03-18, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-374-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-374-2
    - Andrew Young: Global Ethics: Our responsibility 1987-03-20, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-375-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-375-2
    - Jesse Jackson: Remarks at Hill Auditorium 1987-03-23, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-376-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-376-2
    - Adelbert H. Jenkins: The psychology of Black experience 1987-03-24, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-377-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-377-2
    - West African Study Tour Orientation 1987-06-18, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-378-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-378-2
    - West African Study Tour Orientation 1987-06-18, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-379-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-379-2
    - West African Study Tour Orientation 1987-06-18, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-380-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-380-2
    - West African Study Tour Orientation 1987-06-18, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-381-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-381-2
    - Prexy Nesbitt: The struggle in Southern Africa: The Frontline States and US Policy 1987-09-23, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-382-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-382-2
    - Nomgcobo Sangweni and Fr. Casimir Paulsen: Detention in South Africa 1987-11-11, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-383-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-383-2
    - CAAS faculty retreat afternoon session 1988-01-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-384-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-384-2
    - CAAS faculty retreat, hiring, cont. 1988-01-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-385-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-385-2
    - Deborah Robinson: A Cross National Survey Research Project: Beninese and Zimbabwean Perception 1988-01-20, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-386-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-386-2
    - Ralph Story: A Tribute to Malcolm X 1988-02-17, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-387-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-387-2
    - Angela Davis: Fighting racism and sexism in the 1980s 1988-03-19, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-388-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-388-2
    - Angela Davis: Fighting racism and sexism in the 1980s 1988-03-19, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-389-1
    - Jesse Jackson: Remarks at Crisler Arena 1988-03-23, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-390-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-390-2
    - Jesse Jackson: Remarks at Crisler Arena 1988-03-23, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-391-1
    - Susan Taylor: Forward! Into the 1990s: The Responsibilities of the Black Student 1988-09-15, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-392-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-392-2
    - Ali Mazrui: Israel and South Africa 1988-09-22, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-393-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-393-2
    - Andrew Young: Israel and South Africa 1988-09-22, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-394-1
    - Manning Marable 1988-11-04, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-395-1
    - Norm Finkelstein 1989-02-14, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-396-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-396-2
    - Norm Finkelstein 1989-02-14, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-397-1
    - Es'kia Mphahlele: Politics and creative literature under apartheid 1989-03-14, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-398-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-398-2
    - Es'kia Mphahlele, Ali Mazrui, David Gordon and Joyce Kirk: US Policy and Southern Africa 1989-03-15, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-399-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-399-2
    - Robert Hemenway: Their Eyes Were Watching God (Zora Neale Hurston) 1989-03-21, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-400-1
    - Ali Mazrui: The novelist's freedom versus the worshippers dignity: The Moral dilemma of Salman Rushdie's The Satanic Verses 1989-03-30, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-401-1
    - Ali Mazrui: The novelist's freedom versus the worshippers dignity: The Moral dilemma of Salman Rushdie's The Satanic Verses 1989-03-30, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-402-1
    - Lemuel Johnson: Farewell reception - Walter Allen and Prof. Ali A. Mazrui 1989-07-21, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-403-1
    - Abdul Alim Muhammad: Empowering the Black Community to take control of its Destiny 1989-09-28, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-404-1
    - Abdul Alim Muhammad: Empowering the Black Community to take control of its Destiny 1989-09-28, audiocassette (Box 34)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-405-1
    - Blondeen Munson: Civil Rights Movement in Ann Arbor 1990-01-15, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-406-1
    - Gertrude Fraser: Tiny Heads and Hands: African-American Midwives 1990-01-16, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-407-1
    - Elsa Barkley Brown: Weaving threads of community: The case of Richmond 1990-01-17, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-408-1
    - Steve Cokely: Tribute to Malcolm X Week 1990-02-20, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-409-1
    - Steve Cokely: Tribute to Malcolm X Week 1990-02-20, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-410-1
    - N. Frank Ukadike: Some trends in contemporary African cinema 1990-03-26, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-411-1
    - N. Frank Ukadike: Some trends in contemporary African cinema 1990-03-26, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-412-1
    - Charles Henry: From the Beloved Community to Common Ground: A Comparison of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. and Jesse Jackson 1990-03-27, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-413-1
    - Babacar Fall, Siba Grovogui and Ernest J. Wilson III: Contemporary African Issues: Structural development law and labor migration 1990-04-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-414-1
    - Mae Henderson: 9/11/90 Mae Henderson (side 1); CAAS 20th Open House (side 2) 1990-09-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-415-1
    - Darnell F. Hawkins: Newspaper coverage of homicides: Who makes the headlines? 1990-09-25, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-416-1
    - George Lamming: Unfinished Journeys 1990-10-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-417-1
    - George Lamming: Roundtable: University Canons 1990-11-02, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-418-1
    - James Anderson: Reflections on Institutional Racism 1990-11-13, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-419-1
    - Carlos Malcolm: Dialogue Among Cultures: Afro-Cuban and Afro-American Influences on Cuban Music 1990-11-29, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-420-1
    - CAAS Open forum 1990-12-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-421-1
    - CAAS Open forum 1990-12-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-422-1
    - Susanne Kocsis: Caribbean Women Writers and the creation of a literary "Self" through biography 1991-02-02, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-423-1
    - Bruce Hare: Do the Right Thing: Film and Discussion 1991-01-23, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-424-1
    - Bruce Hare: Do the Right Thing: Film and Discussion 1991-01-23, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-425-1
    - Sylvia Pedraza: Discrimination vs. Exclusion: The Experience of Immigrants vs. Racial Minorities in America 1991-03-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-426-1
    - A. Leon Higginbotham: An Open Letter to Justice Clarence Thomas 1992-02-14, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-427-1
    - Hilbourne A. Watson: Global Restructuring Free Trade Zones and the Caribbean 1992-03-12, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-428-1
    - James Chaffers: Giving Shape to the 21st Century 1991-03-14, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-429-1
    - Glen Richards 1991-03-21, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-430-1
    - Babatunde Lawal: Art for Life's Sake in Africa: Images on the Living Dead Among the Yoruba 1991-03-22, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-431-1
    - Earl Lewis: The Social Construction of Race 1991-03-28, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-432-1
    - Earl Lewis: The Social Construction of Race 1991-03-28, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-433-1
    - Anna Vakil: Community-based Housing in African Cities: Case Studies from Zimbabwe 1991-04-11, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-434-1
    - Joe W. Trotter, Jr.: Black Labor in the Urban South 1991-04-17, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-435-1
    - M. Tshitshi Mbatha, Moffat Mogane and Pamela F. Scully: Towards a Post-Apartheid South Africa 1991-04-18, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-436-1
    - Perlita Muiruri and Max Gordon: Dakar and Harare: AAF Viewpoints 1991-09-13, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-437-1
    - Martin Bernal: Black Athena' and her Enemies 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-438-1
    - Martin Bernal: Black Athena' and her Enemies 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-439-1
    - Dorceta E. Taylor: Developing an Environmental Justice Agenda: Minorities in the American and British Environmental Movements 1992-02-17, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-440-1
    - bell hooks: Feminist Theory as Liberatory Practice 1992-02-20, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-441-1
    - Faculty and students: Africana studies: A student faculty dialogue on teaching and the curriculum 1992-03-19, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-442-1
    - Faculty and students: Africana studies: A student faculty dialogue on teaching and the curriculum 1992-03-19, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-443-1
    - Tony Gleaton: The African Presence in the Americas 1992-03-31, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-444-1
    - Murry DePillars: Meet the artist 1992-04-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-445-1
    - Murry DePillars: Meet the artist 1992-04-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-446-1
    - Vincent P. Garcia and Demetrius Bady: Jumping In: The Production and Reproduction of Gang Membership in Late Capitalism 1992-09-28, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-447-1
    - James Johnson, Jr.: The Los Angeles Rebellion of 1992: A Retrospective View 1992-10-15, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-448-1
    - Regina Freer: A Slice of the Pie: Roots of the Black-Korean Conflict 1992-11-12, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-449-1
    - Roderick K. Linzie: The Administration's Response to University of Michigan Anti-racist Student Protests 1992-10-27, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-450-1
    - James Chaffers, Robert Chrisman, Duchess Harris, Laurita Kaigler, Robin D.G. Kelley and Samuel Craig Watkins: Spike Lee and the Black Agenda: A discussion of the new film, Malcolm X 1992-12-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-451-1
    - James Chaffers, Robert Chrisman, Duchess Harris, Laurita Kaigler, Robin D.G. Kelley and Samuel Craig Watkins: Spike Lee and the Black Agenda: A discussion of the new film, Malcolm X 1992-12-04, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-452-1
    - Tanaquil Jones, Ahmad Abdur-Rahman and Dhoruba al-Mujahid bin Wahad: [Black Panther Movement] 1993-01-21, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-453-1
    - Tanaquil Jones, Ahmad Abdur-Rahman and Dhoruba al-Mujahid bin Wahad: [Black Panther Movement] 1993-01-21, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-454-1
    - Tanaquil Jones, Ahmad Abdur-Rahman and Dhoruba al-Mujahid bin Wahad: [Black Panther Movement] 1993-01-21, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-455-1
    - Tanaquil Jones, Ahmad Abdur-Rahman and Dhoruba al-Mujahid bin Wahad: [Black Panther Movement] 1993-01-21, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-456-1
    - Susan Nkomo: Women in the South African Liberation Struggle 1993-02-19, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-457-1
    - M. Nyathi: Memorial for Chris Hani, a South African activist 1993-04-14, audiocassette (Box 35)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-458-1
    - Cruse Symposium 1993-04-22, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-459-1
    - Cruse Symposium 1993-04-22, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-460-1
    - Valerie Smith: Class and Gender in Narratives of Passing 1993-10-21, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-461-1
    - Representation of African Culture in Museums 1993-12-01, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-462-1
    - Representation of African Culture in Museums 1993-12-01, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-463-1
    - Charles Eisendrath: WUOM Interview 1994-03-04, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-464-1
    - Marian Wright Edelman: Commencement 1995-03, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-465-1
    - Matthew Countryman: Industrial Age 1995-12-02, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-466-1
    - Ali Mazrui and John Walters: Interview 1996-02-19, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-467-1
    - Carol Stack 1996-02-27, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-468-1
    - Nell Irvin Painter: Black Woman's Seminar 1996-10-02, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-469-1
    - Loretta Ross: Black Woman's Seminar 1996-10-23, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-470-1
    - Carole Boyce Davis: Black Woman's Seminar 1996-11-13, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-471-1
    - Katie Cannon: Black Woman's Seminar 1997-02-04, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-472-1
    - Barbara Arnwine: Black Woman's Seminar 1997-03-04, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-473-1
    - Leith Mullins: Black Woman's Seminar 1997-03-19, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-474-1
    - Kimberly Crenshaw: Black Woman's Seminar 1997-04-11, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-475-1
    - Sharon Hicks Bartlett 1996-04-19, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-476-1
    - Lansana Kaba, Judith Byfield, Ibrahim Sundiata, Ajayi-Soyinka, Gwendolyn Mikell, Jeanne Toungara and Ali Mazrui: Panel on Henry Louis Gates "Wonders of the African World" 1999-11-13, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-477-1
    - Edith Carney: Interview 2001-05-29, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-478-1
    - Boubacar Barry undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-479-1
    - Judith A. Byfield: Women, Marriage, Divorce and the Emerging Colonial State in Abeokuta (Nigeria) 1892-1904 undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-480-1
    - Louis Farrakhan: Michigan State University undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-481-1
    - Louis Farrakhan: Michigan State University undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-482-1
    - Sherman James: John Henryism and the Health of African Americans undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-483-1
    - Heinz Klug: Defining the Property Rights of Others undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-484-1
    - Earl Lewis: A Conversation with Myself about Race undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-485-1
    - Stella Taylor: Oral History Interview undated, audiocassette (Box 36)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-486-1
- U-Matic Videotapes 1971-1989
  - Undated
    - Undated Central Michigan University students discussing being black; black men and black women; and being black at a white university, etc. (Box 37)
    - Undated--Harold Cruse, Orientation Tape: "AAS 699: Graduate Seminar", 30 min (Box 37)
    - Undated--Harold Cruse, "Black Literature, Objective Criticism of the Arts" (Interview), 60 min (Box 37)
    - Undated William Ford, "Blacks in the Contemporary Business World: Employment Problems" (Interview), 30 min (Box 37)